This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
After the War of the Best in Marineford, Luffy was transported to the Maiden Island,
where grief over the loss of Ace consumed him.
You still have something left in this world to treasure, don't you?
Reunited with Dark King Rayleigh, decision time for Luffy!
Oh, listen, I think the kid stopped screaming.
Yeah, about that.
Where did Straw Hat run off to anyway?
I mean, he's gonna die if that wound opens up, right?
Huh?
Ah!
I got one! Nice!
Huh?
Hey, what the hell?
I think I saw something moving.
Whoa!
It's huge!
Damn!
That is the biggest sea king I've ever seen!
Why is it flipping out?
It's scary!
It's dead!
Something killed it!
You gotta be joking!
I didn't get a look at what happened!
I don't think I like this place!
Whoa!
Is that a man?
Hey!
Who are you?
What a doozy!
Whoa!
It's you!
The Dark King Silver's Rayleigh!
What?
Oh, it's been a while.
I remember meeting you at Saba Odie.
It's Gold Rogers' first mate right here in the flesh!
So, funny story.
Things got kind of rocky in the storm.
My ship sank so I had no choice but to swim in.
The End of the War.
Oh, what a doozy.
It's you!
The Dark King Silver's Rayleigh!
What?
It's you!
The Dark King Silver's Rayleigh!
What?
Oh, it's been a while.
I remember meeting you at Saba Odie.
It's Gold Rogers' first mate right here in the flesh!
So, funny story.
Things got kind of rocky in the storm.
so I had no choice but to swim here.
What?
But they never have storms in this part of the sea.
That's why they call it the Calm Belt.
But then that must mean...
He crashed in safe waters and swam through that bed of sea kings?
How is that supposed to work?
I have a pretty good breaststroke.
Right. He says it like it's no big deal.
So you killed that giant thing...
with your bare hands?
I have actual bare hands and I couldn't do that.
Forgive me, Dark King.
What are you even sorry for?
Let me be frank.
Something tells me Luffy's on this island.
Is that correct?
Have you heard the news?
The princess and some others just left to deliver food to Luffy.
They're so lucky.
I want to make those cheeks of his stretch and stretch and stretch.
I heard they'll invite him over once all his wounds heal.
It should be any day now.
We should hold a feast again.
It's a shame he's hurt, but I'm glad he came back so soon.
Men sure are fascinating creatures, aren't they?
I wish I could be one just for a little while so I could have fun and be stretchy too.
He shall stretch enough for all of us!
Well, since he's here again, maybe I'll make him another pair of clothes.
Without all the frills.
How shameful it is for newlyweds to be separated like this. What a tragic heroine I've become.
Sweetie, don't say that. You know, we're always together in spirit.
Of course, dear.
No matter how far apart the world may keep us, we are bound by a thread of passion.
Oh, Luffy. You always know just what to say. My heart is aflame with affection. I can feel the desire building up inside me.
You are hopeless! How foolish! I've told you, any man may remember your name, but that doesn't mean that you're married!
Oh? Then what is marriage? What else is there to do?
That is a difficult question to answer.
You're too weak to travel to Saba Ori, especially with that wound.
I'll make it work. I gotta see my friends as soon as possible. They'll be expecting me. I promised them I'd be there.
Well, nevertheless.
Now that's odd. The submarine is gone. Surely they didn't depart.
Oh, hello there, Luffy.
Huh? It's Rayleigh, the old guy.
Straightforward as ever, I see.
Why are you here? I was about to use my Viva card to go to Saba Ori, since my friend should be waiting there.
So, did you see them?
I haven't. Actually, it seems they haven't made it there yet.
As for my Viva card, I ended up handing it off to Shaki. It's rather nice.
No one can find me, and I can go wherever I please.
Dark King Rayleigh, I don't believe this. Is it really you?
Hm. You must be that former warlord.
Yeah, that's right. You saved my life at Marineford.
Hm?
Something wrong?
I didn't expect to come face to face with a living legend.
Huh. I suppose you'd like your hat back.
Oh, yeah. Thanks.
My head just doesn't feel right without it. There, that's a lot better.
Hm.
Have you seen a group of pirates or a submarine around here?
If you're talking about Trafalgar Law, he took off.
He left a message for Luffy.
Stay in bed for two more weeks.
He saved your life, didn't he?
Now that was a raw deal. All those women right there.
And we were stuck on the shore. Man, what a tease.
They said bears were welcome to visit, though.
Hey, don't tell us that!
I'm sorry.
Who cares?
I wonder what the Dark King is up to.
Seems he's drawn to another man with the will of Dee.
Hm.
Well, whatever happens, it's bound to be a storm.
No! It can't be! Rayleigh, is that really you?
Oh, why hello, Gloriosa.
It sure has been a while.
Hi, Rayleigh. How are you?
I'm lovely. Good to see you.
It's Luffy!
Could you show some manners for once?
Don't ignore the man who saved your life.
He saved your life so the three of you know old man Rayleigh too?
Indeed.
It's a long story. We'll spare you the details.
I'm so glad to see that you're well.
I've been awake for days worrying about you.
You must be starving.
I've brought plenty of food. Please eat to your heart's content.
You can't even bear to look at him.
How is this marriage of yours supposed to work out?
Serve the man!
Give him some food and be quick about it!
No, Jinbei!
This cornucopia was not meant for you!
You may have one bite.
How generous.
I shall endeavor to curb my appetite.
Come, Luffy.
You need your strength.
And as they say,
to eat is to live.
Well done.
Back to the old Luffy already.
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
No!
Ha!
I said a bite!
Keep stuffing your face like that and you'll leave poor Luffy with nothing!
Hm?
A letter from Shaki.
Thank you for bringing this, Rayleigh.
She hasn't changed.
Not one bit.
Yeah.
If you were living in Sabaody again,
it'd be just like old times.
She's doing well.
And you girls.
You three have gotten tough over the past 13 years,
possessing a strength that is only matched by your beauty.
Rayleigh, Granny Nyon, and Shaki.
If it weren't for you three, we'd still be slaves to the Celestial Dragons right now.
This troubles me.
If you found him, protecting Luffy may be more difficult than we thought.
I know you're friends, but if you could find Luffy so quickly, I fear the Navy's search for him may prove successful as well.
Then we'd all be in danger.
Oh.
If it isn't Rayleigh.
It's me, Hancock.
Do you remember me?
Really?
You just now noticed him?
Don't worry.
I doubt the Navy will guess that Luffy's staying here.
First off, the one who helped him escape from the Sabaody Archipelago told me he sent him off in this direction.
Huh?
Kuma?
I work for the Revolutionary Army. Because Straw Hat shares a connection with Dragon, I will let his crew escape.
Oh, that's quite the twist.
So, where did he end up sending our monkey boy?
Beats me.
I apologize for my abrupt manner earlier.
Can I speak with you for a moment?
I don't have much time.
Not as myself.
Now, as for Straw Hat.
Kuma would only tell me what direction he sent our friend Luffy flying in.
But even that info didn't necessarily point to this island.
However, some interesting details came to light when I was looking into the events leading up to Marineford.
Namely, the Impel Down prison break caused by Luffy and the others.
I spent a lot of time puzzling over how Luffy was able to infiltrate such a heavily guarded prison.
It made enough sense that Luffy got there by stowing away on a Navy ship with Hancock.
But it still didn't add up.
Hmm.
Hancock is known to hate both the world government and men.
I don't think she'd willingly get on a government ship.
Certainly not to help a man.
Knowing that, how else would Luffy have gotten there?
Have you considered this one?
Maybe Hancock met Monkey and had a case of love at first sight.
If so, everything fits.
He is pretty cute, after all.
It's also a lovely way to spite the Navy.
And now she's got the perfect opportunity to nurse her poor, injured lover boy back to hell.
I think you're letting your imagination get carried away, Shaki.
Guess that's the power of women's intuition.
That's my Shaki.
The snake princesses.
Well, see for yourself.
Do you like it?
Please say yes.
It's all just for you.
Although our little theory turned out to be true, it's still pretty ridiculous.
So the Navy won't act on it.
All right. It's time we got down to business.
Hey, Luffy.
Earlier you said you're heading back to Saboori to meet up with your crew.
Do you still plan on doing that?
Of course I do. They need me.
Maybe they do.
But is that the best choice?
Think back.
Surely you remember how your last trip to Saboori ended.
Surely you remember how your last trip to Sabahodi ended.
Everyone!
Start running and look after yourselves!
We can't win this one!
We're too weak!
Get moving!
I couldn't save any of them.
What's wrong with me?
I...
I know, but I...
Do you want to be reunited with your friends only to endure the same fate?
I...
I would imagine that your answer is no.
So let me offer you some advice.
Do with it what you will.
I...
Usoppin!
Don't try to stop me!
Usopp seems to be moving his massive body,
which has grown huge from eating an abundant variety of food
from the gorging forest.
Some might call it running.
Usoppin! It's impossible!
No, it's not. I'll keep trying till I get it.
I can do it this time!
There you are!
Get out of my way, you big oaf!
Special attack!
Oh, no! Usoppin!
Why won't you heed my warnings?
Damn it! So close!
You can't do this!
Every time you try to get off of the Island Inn,
terrifying creatures like the Giant Beetle Inn
will stand in your way
and force you back into the forest inn.
There's nothing to stop you from entering the Island Inn,
but then your fate is sealed!
Even if you can learn to survive in the forest,
no one ever leaves this Island Inn alive!
And don't forget, my name is Heracles Inn!
Huh? Usoppin?
Where did you go?
Oh, no!
The Sea Creature Inn has just crawled onto the Island Inn!
Usoppin!
You're in danger!
The sweet flavors and intoxicating aromas that emanate from the Bowen Islands
attract a plethora of giant insects and birds.
Even sea kings and other aquatic animals visit from time to time.
It's a sea hippo!
Now's not the time to stop and stare!
The wonderful smells lead them deeper onto the Island.
There, they find ever more tempting flavors.
But while it's easy to enter the Island,
it's much harder to leave.
Another one!
Try my Exploding Star!
I'm getting out of here no matter what it takes!
Don't you dare get in my way!
I'll make it back to Sabaoni or die trying!
They're all waiting for me!
Exploding Star!
Usoppin!
The Islands are gonna move again!
Wait, do what now?
Usoppin!
Grab a tree and hang on!
How often does this happen?
Every time it needs to feed!
The so-called Bowen Islands are not at all what they appear.
The flower-shaped island is actually an island-sized flower known as the Stomach Bearer.
Sumper!
What has gotten into you?
Ever since the news coup brought that paper, you've been acting like a maniac!
You've been acting like a maniac. What did it say?
I can't be here!
I have to go!
I've wasted enough time on this stupid island!
Luffy, he lost his brother in the war!
And now, he doesn't know where we are or if we're alive!
Luffy wouldn't let me suffer like that!
I'm his friend! I need to be there for him!
I'm sorry, Luffy!
Worried about their captain, the Straw Hat Pirates concoct plans for a speedy escape.
Unfortunately for Nami, this lands her in a jail cell.
Meanwhile, Frankie searches for a ship that can deliver him from his frozen surroundings.
A trip to a secret lab gives him hope and danger alive.
On the next, One Piece, back to our captain!
A jailbreak at the Sky Island and the Incident on the Winter Island!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
irgendwie a freak moves on Thursday and a stop to dive?
Why does that?!
But if we're not serious, there is someone that involves some suchese guy that you can get away,
you can attack him up the pleas.
Even when he's not to the Nami and the ول higher, the night is the first time from home.
But, there are loads and there's gak guys who can affect us!
There are so many times.
We can all the time.
But, besides the time ones let's z ski up, they do my best and I promise!
Swapping bili, Jumai, yep!
On the next, one at all.
To the Doctor of the one!
The Spetsman autonomy is impressive.
Kärst!
They got now, thank you very much.
It was very nice.
Not strange, we'll have to do your best future bet
Heavenlysis!